Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 3 Locals, 2.
  - Local 315 (Illion)
    - Local 315 (Illion) Incoming Correspondence, June 7, 1945-October 25, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Samuel Rizzo Regarding Local 315 Officers with Fitzgerald Letter to Michael Jimenez, January 8, 1948; 13.
      - Fitzgerald to Cronin Regarding Local 315 Clambake, August 12, 1946; 14.
      - James Matles to O'Bryan Regarding Finances, June 11, 1948; 15.
      - Donald Pinkston to Reynold Fennell Regarding Publicity, March 19, 1947; 16.
      - Ben Risin to Fennell Regarding Arbitration, March 25, 1947; 17.
      - David Scribner to Fennell Regarding Overtime and Incentive, February 1, 1946; 18.
    - Local 315 (Illion) Outgoing Correspondence, November 1, 1945-June 11, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Barbara Cronin to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 315 Clambake, August 8, 1946; 1.
      - Cronin to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 325 Clambake, August 8, 1946; 2.
      - Cronin to General Executive Board Regarding Local 1102, Factionalism and South Organization, March 24, 1947; 3.
      - Cronin to David Ratner Regarding Local 315 Rem-Rand Strikes and Finances, August 7, 1947; 4.
      - Cronin to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 22, 1947; 5.
      - Cronin to Michael Jimenez Regarding Local 315 Rem-Rand Contracts, January 8, 1948; 6.
      - Robert Crossway to Emspak Regarding Finances, Local 315 Rem-Rand Strike, and Dues, December 8, 1947; 7.
      - Reynold Fennell to David Scribner Regarding Incentive and Overtime, January 28, 1946; 8.
      - Fennell Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 315 Rem-Rand Strikes, June 2, 1947; 9.
      - Isabel Gage to UE Regarding Jurisdictions, November 1, 1945; 10.
      - Robert Gould to UE, July 27, 1946; 11.
      - John Kinner to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, June 18, 1945; 12.
      - Elma Luther to Emspak Regarding Local 315 Rem-Rand Strikes, July 2, 1947; 13.
      - Robert Moulton to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 11, 1948; 14.
    - Local 315 (Illion) Outgoing Correspondence, February 26, 1946-November 22, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - E. J. O'Bryan to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Rem-Rand, May 13, 1948; 1.
      - O'Bryan to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances and Dues, May 26, 1948; 2.
      - O'Bryan to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 18-September 15, 1948; 3-4.
      - O'Bryan to Emspak Regarding Finances, Taft-Hartley and Local 315 Rem-Rand Collective Bargaining, November 9, 1948; 5.
      - O'Bryan to Philip Murray Regarding International Association of Machinists and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and Congress of Industrial Organizations, November 11, 1948; 6.
      - O'Bryan to David Scribner Regarding Staff Finances, November 22, 1948; 7.
      - O'Bryan Telegram Regarding Membership Meeting, 8.
      - Thomas Shepard to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 26, 1946; 9.
      - Shepard to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off, November 7, 1946; 10.
      - Local 315 Executive Board Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances, August 4, 1947; 11.
      - Local 315 Executive Board Telegram to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 4, 147; 12.
      - A Reader to UE News Regarding Local 315 Rem-Rand Strikes, January 8, 1948; 13.
    - Local 315 (Illion) Organization, April 13-May 7, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Diantha Hoag to Julius Emspak, April 13, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, April 18, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Hoag, April 18, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak Secretary to Hoag, May 1, 1945; 4.
      - Hoag to Ray Klausner, May 1, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Hoag, May 7, 1945; 6.
    - Local 315 (Illion) Subsidy, November 8, 1949-January 19, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Michael Jimenez to James Matles, November 8, 1949; 1.
      - Matles to Jimenez, November 11, 1949; 2.
      - Jimenez to David Ratner, December 7, 1949; 3.
      - Matles to Jimenez, December 14, 1949-January 11, 1950; 4-5.
      - Jimenez Telegram to Matles, January 13, 1950; 6.
      - Matles to Jimenez, January 19, 1950; 7.
    - Local 315 (Illion) Proposed Contract Comparison and Correspondence, November 24, 1947-January 7, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Comparison of Proposed Elmira International Association of Machinists and Illion UE Contracts, November 24, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Michael Jimenez Regarding Finances, January 7, 1948; 2.
      - David Ratner Telegram to Charles Rivers Regarding Finances, 3.
    - Local 325 (Illion) Rem-Rand Bulletin, October 6-9, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Local 315 (Illion) Newspaper Clippings, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - "Priests Urge Defeat of UE in Rand Election" Utica Daily Press, 1950; 1.
  - Local 316
    - Local 316 Constitution, September 1943 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Constitution with September 2, 1943, Stephen Jaszka Letter to Towsen, September 1943; 1.
    - Local 316 Officers Lists, November 18, 1946-April 8, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Local 316 Incoming Correspondence, July 27, 1945-February 25, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - Joseph Dermody to James Green, March 27, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Edward Bishop, July 27, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Dues Check-off, February 25, 1947; 3.
      - David Ratner to Green Regarding Catskill Metal, March 12, 1946; 4.
    - Local 316 Outgoing Correspondence, July 23, 1945-February 24, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Edward Bishop to Julius Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 23, 1945; 1.
      - Bishop to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off and Poughkeepsie General Electric, February 24, 1947; 2.
      - James Green to James Matles Regarding Unemployment and Finances, January 22, 1946; 3.
      - Green to Matles Regarding Catskill Metal, March 23, 1946; 4.
    - Local 316 Pratt and Letchworth, February 6-10, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - Charter Application, February 6, 1942; 1.
      - Ted Buczek to James Matles, February 10, 1942; 2.
    - Local 316 Standard Gage, May 16-21, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - Walter Wofford to Julius Emspak, May 16, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Wofford, May 21, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, May 21, 1945; 3.
    - Local 316 Schenectady, October 2, 1963-April 6, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Local 316 Standard Gage Strike, September 7-October 1, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - Report of Strike, September 7, 1945; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, October 1, 1945; 2.
    - Local 316 Correspondence, March 23, 1947-March 26, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - James Green to Julius Emspak Regarding General Electric, Dues Check-off, Local 316 Amalgamation and Political Action, March 23, 1947; 1.
      - Green to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Standard Gage, March 26, 1948; 2.
  - Local 317
    - Local 317 Incoming Correspondence, January 12-September 20, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - Julius Emspak to Peter Cudney Regarding Finances, January 12, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Harold Vrooman Regarding Finances, January 12, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Lewis Benedict Regarding Finances and National Labor Relations Board, January 15, 1943; 3.
      - Leo Jandreau to Lewis Benedict Regarding Local 317 Disbanding, September 20, 1943; 4.
    - Local 317 Outgoing Correspondence, August 1943 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Louis Benedict to Leo Jandreau Regarding Middletown, August 1943; 1.
      - Benedict to Jandreau Regarding Mailing List, 2.
    - Local 317 Lost Time Staff Expenses, December 15, 1942-January 9, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - Lou Sarti to Leo Jandreau, December 15, 1942; 1.
      - Willard Bliss to Jandreau, December 24, 1942; 2.
      - Jandreau to James Matles, January 5, 1943; 3.
      - Matles to Ruth Stevens, January 8, 1943; 4.
      - Stevens to Matles, January 9, 1943; 5.
    - Local 317 Clemson Brothers, March 9-23, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Julius Emspak to Louis Sarti, March 9, 1943; 1.
      - Maurice Cesarotti to Emspak, March 23, 1943; 2.
    - Local 317 Correspondence, January 1942 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - Louis Sarti to Leo Jandreau Regarding National Labor Relations Board, January 1942; 1.
  - Local 317 (Jamestown)
    - Local 317 (Jamestown) Officers Lists, January 9, 1947-December 7, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Local 317 (Jamestown) Incoming Correspondence, July 23, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Julius Emspak to G. A. Rosengren Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 23, 1945; 1.
    - Local 317 (Jamestown) Outgoing Correspondence, July 16, 1945-February 12, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Bernard Mason to UE Regarding Dues, October 27, 1950; 1.
      - Robert Mason to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Dues, February 12, 1951; 2.
      - G. A. Rosengren to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 16, 1945; 3.
    - Local 317 (Jamestown) Organization, September 16-October 11, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 90)
      - Willard Bliss to Julius Emspak, September 16, 1944; 1.
      - Bliss to Ray Klausner, October 6, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, October 11, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Bliss, October 11, 1944; 4.
    - Local 317 (Jamestown) Correspondence, November 1, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - Julius Emspak to Michael Jimenez, November 1, 1950; 1.
  - Local 318
    - Local 318 Officers Lists, July 1947-June 1948 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Local 318 Incoming Correspondence, March 12, 1945-November 2, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - Julius Emspak to S. Aloi Regarding Veterans and Dues, March 12, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak Secretary to Monroe Milliman Regarding Dues, March 25, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Milliman Regarding Membership Drive, April 10, 1947; 3.
      - Leo Jandreau to All Locals Regarding Rem-Rand, and United Auto Workers and Congress of Industrial Organizations Inter-union Rivalry with Jandreau Letter, Contract Copy, Congressional Record Excerpt and November 2, 1948, Michael Jimenez Letter to John Mavrillo, November 1, 1948; 4.
    - Local 318 Outgoing Correspondence, March 21, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - Monroe Milliman to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Membership Drive, March 21, 1947; 1.
    - Local 318 Ledger, 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Local 318 Organization, March 11-21, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - Willard Bliss to Julius Emspak, March 11, 1944; 1.
      - Emspak to Bliss, March 20, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Jandreau, March 21, 1944; 3.
    - Local 318 Membership Drive, March 25-April 2, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 97)
      - Julius Emspak to Leo Jandreau, March 25, 1947; 1.
      - Jandreau to Emspak, April 2, 1947; 2.
    - Local 318 United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, January 6-10, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 98)
      - John Mavrillo to Michael Jimenez, January 6, 1949; 1.
      - Mimenez to James Matles, January 10, 1949; 2.
    - Local 318 Disbanding, January 31-February 3, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 99)
      - Richard Linsley to Julius Emspak with Bank Statement, January 31, 1949; 1.
      - Linsley to Emspak, February 3, 1949; 2.
    - Local 318 Correspondence and Notification, March 1946-February 1948 (Box 5, Folder 100)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Rem-Rand, March 19, 1946; 1.
      - Walter Wofford to Julius Emspak, February 1948; 2.
    - Local 318 Rem-Rand Bulletin, October 26, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Local 318 Rem Rambler, October 27, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Local 318 Leaflets, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - A Message from the Workers in Ilion Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 29, 1948; 1.
      - A Ball and Chain Contract Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 2.
      - Facts - Not Falses Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 3.
      - Discharge Clause Regarding IAM Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 4.
      - Here's the Score Regarding IAM and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 5.
      - One Union in Rem Rand Regarding IAM Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 6.
      - Slander Regarding IAM Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 7.
      - IAM Sells OUT Grievance Clauses Regarding IAM Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 8.
  - Local 318 (Niagara Falls)
    - Local 318 (Niagara Falls) Charter Application, March 28, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Local 319
    - Local 319 Officers Lists, August 1943-December 1954 (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Lists, August 1943-January 1947; 1-2.
      - List with Leo Jandreau Letter, February 11, 1947; 3.
      - Lists, February 1947-December 1954; 4-16.
    - Local 319 Incoming Correspondence, October 30, 1942-November 18, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Al Clough to E. P. Voland Regarding Supplies, November 24, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Voland Regarding Supplies, Dues and Military Personnel, October 30, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Voland Regarding War Labor Board, December 3, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Voland Regarding Wages and Literature, January 25, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Voland Regarding Supplies and Dues, January 27, 1949; 5.
      - Emspak to Josephine Sionko Regarding Finances and Supplies, July 20, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak to Voland Regarding Veterans and Dues, January 23, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Delos Fletcher Regarding Finances, August 13, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Robert Gladstone Regarding Supplies, May 24, 1946; 9.
      - Emspak to Gordis Knapp Regarding General Executive Board, Februray 25, 1947; 10.
      - Emspak to Peter Breier Regarding Dues Check-off, June 8, 1948; 11.
      - Emspak to Breier Regarding National Strike Fund, November 18, 1952; 12.
      - Leo Jandreau to N. H. Forsyth Regarding Buffalo United Labor Council and Factionalism with Jandreau Letter to Harriet Warren, December 13, 1943; 13.
      - David Ratner to Voland Regarding Finances and Lost Time, August 22, 1944; 14.
      - Convention Committee to Peter Breier Regarding 1948 UE Convention, August 4-11, 1948; 15-16.
    - Local 319 Outgoing Correspondence, October 24, 1942-December 10, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - Peter Breier to Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing List, Dues and Supplies, May 10, 1948; 1.
      - Breier to Convention Committee Regarding 1948 UE Convention, August 6, 1948; 2.
      - Breier to Emspak Regarding Local 319 Officers, January 10, 1949; 3.
      - Breier to UE Regarding Local 319 Officers, December 10, 1951; 4.
      - Gordis Knapp to UE Regarding General Executive Board, February 20, 1947; 5.
      - Mary Kuehn to UE Regarding Constitutions, January 7, 1943; 6.
      - E. P. Voland to UE Regarding War Labor Board, December 1, 1942; 7.
      - Voland to Emspak Regarding Dues and Military Personnel, October 24, 1942; 8.
      - Voland to Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, January 22, 1943; 9.
      - Voland to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 26, 1943; 10.
      - Voland to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, January 13, 1944; 11.
      - Voland to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 12, 1944; 12.
    - Local 319 Bonding Form, June 26, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Local 319 Organization, June 22-23, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - Al Clough to James Matles, June 22, 1942; 1-2.
      - Charter Application, June 22, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Clough, June 23, 1942; 4.
    - Local 319 North Tonawanda Battenfeld Grease and Oil Company, August 22, 1979-April 6, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Local 319 Strike, April-September 1946 (Box 5, Folder 111)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, April 9, 1946; 1.
      - Report of Strike, April 22, 1946; 2.
      - Termination of Strike, September 1946; 3.
    - Local 319 Strike, Subsidies and Other Monies, November 20, 1968-October 10, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Local 319 Agreement, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Local 319 Collective Bargaining, May 1-15, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 114)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, May 1, 1947; 1.
      - Emanuel Fried Telegram to James Matles, May 15, 1947; 2.
    - Local 319 Correspondence, October 30, 1942-July 30, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 115)
      - Julius Emspak to Willard Bliss Regaring Finances, October 30, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Bliss Regarding Dues, October 29, 1943; 2.
      - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Finances, Per Capita and Local 319 Officers, July 30, 1945; 3.
    - Local 319 Pamphlet, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 116)
      - Facts about Ue Regarding Buffalo Bolt Organization, 1942; 1.
    - Local 319 Newspaper Clippings, May 8, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 117)
      - "Why We Strike" Daily Press, May 8, 1946; 1.
  - Local 320
    - Local 320 Officers Lists, November 6, 1947-September 22, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Local 320 Resolutions, April 19, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Local 320 Incoming Correspondence, September 22, 1942-February 17, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 120)
      - Julius Emspak to Richard Sullivan Regarding Finances, September 22, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to G. Money Regarding Finances, November 18, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Alwyne Kent Regarding Executive Order 9240, May 11, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Kent Regarding Supplies, July 9, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Kent Regarding Staff Members, August 27, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to John Baston Regarding Dues, July 5, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak to Tom Morrissey Regarding Finances, July 20, 1944; 7.
      - Emspak to John Baston Regarding Veterans and Dues, April 4, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Mark Clancy Regarding Dues and Membership Drive, February 17, 1948; 9.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to John Baston Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, April 15, 1946; 10.
      - Leo Jandreau to Kent Regarding Wages and Dispatchers, November 22, 1943; 11.
      - Jandreau to Kent Regarding General Electric Contracts, December 14, 1943; 12.
      - Jandreau to Baston Regarding Unemployment and Seniority, January 21, 1944; 13.
      - Jandreau Telegram to John Lynch Regarding Membership Meetings, February 8, 1944; 14.
      - Russ Nixon to Fay Marvin Regarding Political Action Committee, November 3, 1947; 15.
    - Local 320 Outgoing Correspondence, May 5, 1943-April 18, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 121)
      - John Baston to Leo Jandreau Regarding Dues and Membership Drive, January 13, 1944; 1.
      - Baston to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Membership Drive, June 7, 1944; 2.
      - Baston to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, March 30, 1945; 3.
      - Robert Bornholz to James Matles Regarding Mailing List, October 6, 1949; 4.
      - Bornholz to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 16, 1949; 5.
      - Mark Clancy to Emspak Regarding Dues and Membership Drive, December 29, 1948; 6.
      - Clancy to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Stewards, January 24, 1949; 7.
      - Lester Earl to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, October 29, 1947; 8.
      - Will Herman Telegram to Joseph Dermody Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, April 18, 1950; 9.
      - Alwyne Kent to Emspak Regarding General Electric and Overtime, May 5, 1943; 10.
      - Kent to Emspak Regarding Publicity, July 7, 1943; 11.
      - Kent to Emspak Regarding Local 320 Officers, August 8, 1943; 12.
      - Kent to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, August 16, 1943; 13.
      - Kent to Emspak Regarding Local 320 Officers, September 15, 1943; 14.
      - Kent to Emspak Regarding General Electric Contracts, September 15, 1943; 15.
      - Kent to Jandreau Regarding General Electric Collective Bargaining and Local 320 Officers Elections, November 23, 1943; 16.
      - Kent to Emspak Regarding General Electric Contracts, November 23, 1943; 17.
      - Kent to Jandreau Regarding Dispatchers Organization and Syracuse General Electric, November 29, 1943; 18.
      - Jeff Lowman Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding UE Officers, September 10, 1948; 19.
      - John Lynch Telegram to Jandreau Regarding Membership Meeting, February 8, 1944; 20.
      - Lynch Telegram to Emspak Regarding Wages, February 16, 1944; 21.
      - Lynch to Emspak Regarding Dues, Membership Drive and Supplies, May 24, 1944; 22.
      - James Monroe to Emspak Regarding Packinghouse Workers Strike, January 28, 1949; 23.
      - Monroe to Richard Linsley Regarding Factionalism and Staff Members, February 8, 1949; 24.
      - Monroe to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and District 3, May 10, 1949; 25.
    - Local 320 Outgoing Correspondence, November 27, 1942-August 15, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 122)
      - Thomas Morrissey to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 320 Officers, December 2, 1943; 1.
      - Morrissey to Joseph Dermody Regarding Local 320 Officers, June 7, 1944; 2.
      - Morrissey to Emspak Regarding Local 320 Officers, June 7, 1944; 3.
      - Ed Rice Telegram to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, August 15, 1947; 4.
      - Frances Siegel to Emspak Regarding Local 320 Officers, November 27, 1942; 5.
    - Local 320 Bonding, January 13-19, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 123)
      - Questionnaire, January 13, 1943; 1.
      - Form, January 19, 1943; 2.
    - Local 320 Arbitration Bill, January 19, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Local 320 Organization, September 18, 1942-October 2, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 125)
      - Julius Emspak to Willard Bliss, September 18, 1942; 1.
      - Bliss to Emspak, October 2, 1942; 2.
    - Local 320 War Labor Board Case, August 17, 1943-January 11, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 126)
      - Sidney Sugerman to General Electric, August 17, 1943; 1.
      - Abram Stockman to General Electric, September 18, 1943; 2.
      - G. H. Pfeif to Leo Jandreau, October 16, 1943; 3.
      - Ben Riskin to Jandreau, October 19, 1943; 4.
      - Jandreau to Riskin, October 22, 1943; 5.
      - Riskin to Stockman, October 1943; 6.
      - Pfeif to Jandreau, December 4, 1943; 7.
      - Jandreau to Pfeif, December 13, 1943; 8.
      - Pfeif to Jandreau, December 15, 1943-January 11, 1944; 9-10.
    - Local 320 Dispatcher Grievances, December 3-13, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 127)
      - Leo Jandreau to G. H. Pfeif, December 3, 1943; 1.
      - Pfeif to Jandreau, December 10, 1943; 2.
      - Jandreau Secretary to A. N. Kent, December 13, 1943; 3.
    - Local 320 Membership Drive, June 2-14, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 128)
      - Julius Emspak to Leo Jandreau, June 2, 1944; 1.
      - Jandreau to Emspak, June 8, 1944; 2.
      - Willard Bliss to Emspak, June 14, 1944; 3.
    - Local 320 Factionalism, January 31-April 5, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 129)
      - Kenneth LaDuke to Congress of Industrial Organization with Petition and LaDuke Statement, January 31, 1946; 1.
      - LaDuke to Congress of Industrial Organization, March 8, 1946; 2.
      - Allan Haywood to LaDuke, March 12, 1946; 3.
      - LaDuke to Haywood, March 16, 1946; 4.
      - Haywood to LaDuke, April 5, 1946; 5.
      - Haywood to Albert Fitzgerald, April 5, 1946; 6.
    - Local 320 Finances, January 24-March 1, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 130)
      - Court Stipulation, January 24, 1950; 1.
      - Samuel Greene to District 3, January 26, 1950; 2.
      - Robert Bornholz to David Ratner, January 26-February 6, 1950; 3-4.
      - James Matles to Bornholz, February 6, 1950; 5.
      - Janet Barish to Richard Linsley, February 23, 1950; 6.
      - Linsley to Ratner, March 1, 1950; 7.
    - Local 313 Correspondence, December 14, 1942-June 9, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 131)
      - Jack Davis to Julius Emspak Regarding General Electric and Conference Board, December 14, 1942; 1.
      - Willard Bliss to Leo Jandreau Regarding Local 320 Officer Elections and Factionalism with Election Results, January 7, 1944; 2.
      - Ben Riskin to Jandreau Regarding War Labor Board, March 17, 1944; 3.
      - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Grievances, March 22, 1944; 4.
      - Fay Marvin to UE Political Action Committee Regarding Political Action Committee, October 8, 1947; 5.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Liverpool General Electric, February 13, 1948; 6.
      - Emspak to Jandreau Regarding Dues and Membership Drive, January 4, 1949; 7.
      - Richard Linsley Telegram to Joseph Dermody Regarding Factionalism and 1949 UE Conference, June 9, 1949; 8.
    - Local 313 Pamphlets, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 132)